This is Brock.
There's an old hunting cabin up here.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Woman: Copy.
Do you want to wait for backup?
Negative. Looks abandoned.
Holy shit.
Hood.
How'd you find me?
I didn't.
I mean, I wasn't looking for you.
I thought you were gone.
Hey, you want to do me a favor
and point that thing somewhere else, okay?
Holy hell.
Haven't seen you in two years.
And all that time you've been
living up in this cabin like some kind of
mountain man or something?
Is anybody here with you?
Then I'm gonna need you to come with me.
I'm not asking.
Sheriff lotus.
That's right.
How does that feel?
Like a hemorrhoid.
You want to tell me what this is about?
I'll tell you down at the station.
You mean the cadi?
No, I don't.
What do you think?
Bulletproof glass.
One-and-a-half-inch-thick polycarb.
Thought you'd like that.
Scott, I need those fingerprint results
as soon as you get them.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
I need to know about the press conference.
Bunker, you remember Mr. Hood?
Deputy Nina Cruz.
Billy raven moved on.
He's the new chief of the kinaho pd.
Woman: Sheriff.
Brock: Helen, any messages?
Woman: On your desk.
- Oh, the FBI?
- Woman: Not yet.
Nice office.
Yes, it is. Can I get
you something to drink?
I got water, coffee.
I've got this Espresso machine here.
Have a seat.
First of all, you should know,
when I went up there today,
you were the last
person I expected to find.
Were you in that cabin two nights ago?
Yes.
- Anybody with you?
- No.
Who's dead?
Who is that?
Rebecca.
Brock: Her body was found yesterday,
near the river.
That's not where she was killed,
but that's where the body was dumped.
Jesus.
Brock: This is the third murder of its kind
that we've had this year.
- You call the FBI?
- Yeah.
I called them after the second one.
And they sent some little shit up here,
and he looked through our files
and took some notes,
and then he ran back to Quantico as fast
as his little $60 loafers could take him.
Told me to call back if
a third body turned up.
So maybe now they'll give a shit.
So, what does this have to do with me?
When was the last time you saw Rebecca?
I haven't seen anyone
for about 18 months.
You know, and yet, it's the weird part,
the last coordinates on her car's GPS
brought me up to your cabin today.
- You didn't see her?
- Nope.
Any idea why she'd come looking for you?
You know, how the hell she even know
you were up there, hood?
I'm just trying to put this together.
- It's her uncle's land.
- It's what?
It's her uncle's land.
You're living on proctor's land?
He doesn't know.
What happened to you, hood?
I retired.
We found trace blood
that didn't match Rebecca's.
I'm gonna need you to, uh,
voluntarily submit a blood sample
so we can rule you out.
What, do you think
I'm a fucking serial killer, now?
Have you seen yourself lately, hood?
You're living up in the woods.
You look like the unabomber.
Yes, you can have my blood.
Oh, and, hood,
if there's anything else you
want to tell me, now's the time.
You should be looking at proctor.
Brock: Yeah, well, these days
that's a little more complicated.
He's...
Yeah?
- Press conference is about to start.
- Oh, shit. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- Sheriff hood.
He's not the sheriff.
Listen, I'll have deputy Cruz
come up and take your blood,
and then she'll give you a lift back.
Take care of yourself.
Lucas: And you are?
Is there something wrong?
Sorry, you just, uh...
You reminded me of someone for a moment.
Mmm.
Deputy who got killed.
Indian gangbanger broke her neck?
I think I like you better
when you don't talk.
Sir.
It's time.
Reporter 1: Mr. Mayor, this is the third
murder of a young woman this year.
Is this a serial killer and...
Reporter 2: Is it true
that the latest victim was your niece?
Reporter 3: Mr. Mayor, why are
the police reports being withheld?
Kai: Here's... here's what we know.
Here's what we know.
Yesterday, the body of Rebecca bowman
was found near the mouth
of the dellwood basin.
She was murdered.
And while the police can't say for certain,
there are definitely similarities
between this case
and the murders of two other young women
that occurred over the last year.
The banshee Sheriff Department
has notified the FBI,
and agents are en route
to assist in the investigation.
And to answer your question,
yes, Rebecca was my niece.
And, yes, you can rest
assured that neither I
nor sheriff lotus and the members
of his department will rest
until we have found
this sick, twisted bastard.
Rebecca: So, this is it?
Kai: Yes, this is it.
Rebecca: It's beautiful.
Kai: I'm going to be mayor,
and you're taking on more
of a leadership role in the business.
I just figured we 'd need something
a bit more secure.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Get out.
What's going on?
Da dismissed the
charges. You're free to go.
You're fucking with us.
You got 10 seconds
before I close that door again.
I knew that arrest was bullshit.
- What was it this time?
- Physical evidence.
They practically strangled that old man.
I know. Da's a real piece of work.
He's a puppet.
Proctor's got his hand up his ass.
But that's a talk for another time.
The walls have ears.
Hey, thanks a lot, officers.
Have a nice evening.
Carrie: There's always some part of me
that's thinking about him.
How he looked when he died.
How he looked at me.
Carrie: There are days when that look
haunts me so badly I can barely breathe.
Man: Hey, hey, hey, hey. Look at this.
Carrie: And then there are days
when I can distract myself.
You lost, honey?
Carrie: Where / can shut off all the noise.
Maybe we can help you find your way.
Oh, I hope so.
Carrie: And just do what I have to do.
Those are the good days.
Carrie: So, you tough guys
like beating up on people, huh?
It wasn't us. They let us go.
Well, they shouldn't have.
Carrie: There's always that moment
when I just wake up
where I think I'm still there.
Still back there in our old house.
And when I roll over,
Gordon will be there lying next to me.
And then I'll hear the kids
stirring in their rooms.
Hubbard: So, how do you handle it?
Carrie: / exercise.
I eat something.
I start working on the house.
Hubbard: How's the house coming along?
Carrie: There's something about working
with my hands that gives me peace.
Hubbard: What else gives you peace?
Carrie: Not much.
Do you find our sessions helpful?
I'm here because it's court-mandated.
No offense.
None taken.
If I vouch for your competency
to parent your children, today,
would you come back?
If I said yes, would you do that?
That's not really how it works.
They had no right to take my kids away.
- You violated the terms of your probation.
- I was abducted.
The military investigation cleared us.
Any association with the criminal element
was enough for social services...
I know.
How many times
are you gonna ruin our lives?
From now on, you're just the asshole
who knocked up my mom.
Please.
What are you doing here?
The manager told me
our former sheriff was on a bender.
Trashing the room.
Playing with guns.
How is that your business?
It's my uncle's motel.
Just leave me alone, would you?
Get the fuck out of here! Go!
Please go.
Rebecca: You can't stay here.
Let me take you back to your place.
No, I can't live there anymore.
- There's ghosts.
- Hmm.
Even before you wrecked it,
this dump is nowhere to live.
Come on. Let's go for a ride.
Rebecca: It's an old hunting cabin.
Hasn't been used in years,
but the water still runs.
Lucas: Whose is it?
Rebecca: Who do you think?
Lucas: You really think
your uncle's gonna let me stay here?
He won't know.
How do you like it?
Yeah.
Rebecca: I thought you would.
No ghosts.
- Does this hurt?
- Not anymore.
I hate that they did this to you.
I had been meaning to get
that tattoo removed anyway.
Just wish it could always be like this.
Maybe one day.
You okay?
Hang on right there.
He'll be with you in a moment.
You fuck.
We have a strict agreement
with the redbones.
You keep your business on the reservation,
and we keep ours off it.
You are in breach of that agreement.
Yeah?
I just got to work, for fuck's sake.
Who's there?
Shit.
No. Okay. Don't do a fucking thing.
I'm coming back to town.
Man: Well, you can ask him yourself.
Things are going fantastic over here.
This time you're buying. Okay.
All right, all right, all right. Great.
Say hi to Carol for me.
Hey there, Calvin. What can I do you for?
I'm not feeling great.
I'm gonna need to go home.
- You look fine.
- I've got a stomach bug.
I thought I could make it
through the day, but I can't.
You're handling the tri-quarterlies,
aren't you?
Mmm-hmm.
They done?
Not yet, no.
Kind of need those done today.
Well, I can take them home with me
and I'll have them done for you
first thing tomorrow.
We were late with them last quarter,
too, weren't we?
I don't think so, no.
I think we were, Calvin.
Gook motherfucker!
I'll have those to you
first thing tomorrow.
What the fuck is he doing here?
We came in and found him here
with this motherfucker already in the vice.
He was dealing in our territory.
The territory you and your men
are charged with protecting.
I brought him here as
a courtesy.
Mmm-hmm.
So my tax dollars aren't enough
for you and your little tribe, huh?
Now you fuckers are going to encroach
on my business?
Fuck you.
I don't think so.
We pay for your houses...
For your damn reservations,
for your school and your health care,
even when all of you were getting rich
off your fucking casinos, right?
This country has lost its spine.
The politicians are giving it away
to the mutts and the mongrels
while good, pure-blooded Americans
go hungry.
This isn't a nation anymore.
It's a fucking soup kitchen!
And you know what?
We're all out of fucking soup!
Thanks for the heads up.
You can tell proctor
that we've got it under control.
Don't use his name in front of outsiders.
Him?
Yeah, I don't think
he's paying too much attention.
You don't want me to come back here.
Hey, sugar.
You disappear for a year and a half,
you show up here looking like
something out of the Bible,
and all you got to say for yourself is
"hey, sugar"?
How you been?
Small talk?
Seriously?
Somebody killed Rebecca bowman.
I know that.
Everybody around here knows that.
Now why do you know that?
Well,
I guess I'm a suspect.
Did you do it?
Look, it's a fair question.
I mean, look at yourself.
Where the hell have you been?
I had to disappear for a while.
Clear my head.
You clear your head for a few days.
A week maybe.
For you, maybe even a month.
But you, you went awol.
And you forgot about your friends
and you forgot about...
I did not forget about job.
How the fuck was hiding away
gonna help him?
You here for your money?
But I do need a car.
Sugar: Only thing I bought.
Figured it might come in handy
if I ever needed a quick exit.
So, what happens now?
I don't know.
But something, right?
Yeah. Something.
Remember, hood,
you're not the sheriff anymore.
I never was.
Sugar: You know what I mean!
What'd the other guy look like?
Ha-ha.
Very fucking funny.
Actually, I wasn't kidding.
What did he look like?
He looked like a fucking asshole
smashing the shit out of my hands.
The guy stuck around long enough
to walk all over your face,
and you didn't even get a look?
It was dark.
Nina: Don't worry.
I got time.
You're back.
Sorry about Rebecca.
What does this have to do with you?
Nothing.
And yet here you are.
Is there anything I should know?
Lucas: Your uncle,
he's not a good man.
Well, then, let me live with you.
I'm not a good man either.
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
You think I had anything to do
with my niece's death?
You may not have killed her,
but you sure as shit got her killed.
As soon as you took her in,
it was only a matter of time.
Yeah.
You may be right.
I'm gonna find that son of a bitch.
But as a mayor,
I'm somewhat hampered
in my ability to clarify matters.
How'd you pull that off?
I ran unopposed.
Of course.
Where would you start?
With the foothills. The boedickers.
- I heard they got burned down.
- It's true.
But Aaron boedicker's still alive.
You guys, you did see
the yellow tape here, right?
Shenfi.
It's fine.
Our work is done here.
Following me, Brock?
Me? No.
That's what deputies are for.
Is hood a suspect?
Well, if he was, you'd be the first
to know it, wouldn't you?
No, Mr. Hood is a person of interest
in this case,
which is something you two have in common.
- Be careful, sheriff.
- I always am, Mr. Mayor.
Just like old times, huh?
Except no one's bleeding.
Yet.
Hey, Kurt.
Come on, bro.
How long are you gonna keep this up, man?
I saved your fucking life, Kurt.
What do you think watts would have done?
He would've had you executed.
I took action before he
could order it, that's it.
I was in the burn unit for two months.
I know and I'm sorry,
but you put me in an impossible situation
and I had to prove my loyalty to the cause.
You know that.
Just come for dinner, man.
Maggie would really love to see you.
And we can work this out.
Brothers before brotherhood,
that's what you always said.
You're not my brother.
What? What the fuck did you just say to me?
I'm the only thing standing
between them and you, asshole.
You better fucking remember that!
- Hey, Carrie.
- Hey, Brock.
The place is really
starting to come together.
- Thanks.
- No.
Looks good.
How are the kids doing?
Oh, you know. Gordon's parents
are driving them crazy.
Something on your mind, Brock?
Listen, Carrie, I don't
know if you've heard,
but hood is back.
Guess you haven't heard.
He's been living up in
the foothills in a cabin.
He, uh... he looks rough.
Just thought you'd want to know.
Yeah.
Call me if you need anything, all right?
Carrie: Okay.
- Have a good day.
- Thanks.
Lewis, is everything okay?
Lewis, come in.
Man: Don't fucking move.
Something funny?
Wait for it.
Lucas: Uh-uh.
Drop it!
You.
Long time, huh?
Why don't you take a seat?
You finally tracked me down
after all these years.
Lucas: Who are you?
My name is Dalton.
Are you military?
I was.
But now I recruit men like you.
I develop them for an elite unit.
What unit?
What branch?
Exactly.
- This is revenge?
- Revenge?
Not really.
Where's job?
How the fuck would I know?
No, no, no, no. You know how this works.
You taught me.
Elbows, insteps, knees.
I can keep you alive for fucking days.
I know, which is why if! Knew something,
I would tell you.
Bullshit.
I didn't take him.
But the man who did knew I would want him.
I paid him his price
and he handed over job.
Then what?
I turned him in.
I cleaned my slate with the powers that be.
- And who are they?
- Oh, come on.
Don't be a fucking idiot.
You know how this works.
Faces without names, names without faces.
Yeah, go ahead.
Go ahead, shoot my other knee.
Go ahead. You know that
it won't change what I'm saying.
I have no idea where they took him.
No, but you can find him.
Black sites, ghost detention centers.
You have access to those files.
Not anymore.
After the congressional hearings,
they closed the loop and I'm not in it.
Bullshit. You are the fucking loop.
I was. That was 20
years ago. Things change.
Why are we even having this conversation?
You know that job is already dead.
No, he has intelligence.
He's a valuable asset.
His intelligence was 20 years old.
He was a fucking trophy grab.
- He was a head on somebody's wall.
- Whose wall?
Dalton: Doesn't matter.
The man's dead.
You know it and I know it.
We got to go. We got to go now!
I guess I'm still in certain loops.
Lucas: Go, go, go!
Did he come to see you?
Yes.
But he's not the man that left that night.
Not anymore.
- Well, did he say where he's been?
- No.
Did he say anything?
You thought he might have a lead on job?
Look, the day he left,
that was the day you needed to stop
looking to him for any answers.
You think job's still alive?
I don't know.
Sometimes I hope he isn't.
Because if he is,
it makes us even bigger assholes
than we already are.
So, you got nothing.
Nothing.
Either he didn't know or he wouldn't say.
He didn't know.
I guess we'll never know now.
Did you really have to kill him?
He didn't know.
Okay.
What's our next play?
We don't have one.
It's over.
Sugar: No.
We don't just give up.
We have no choice.
So, what?
- You're done?
- We got nothing.
- So we find something.
- We've got nothing.
- I can't just leave him for dead.
- Do you think I want to?
Don't you think I'd do anything?
Dalton was right.
He was right.
Job was dead from the moment
he handed him over.
Where the hell are you going?
Lucas: He's dead.
Anybody home?
Hello?
Daddy!
What's up, little man?
- Where's your mommy?
- Upstairs.
Yeah?
Babe, I'm home!
Maggie: Coming.
God, you got bigger.
What do you weigh, like 1,000 pounds?
- No.
- What, are you, like, 10 feet tall?
- Okay, maybe tomorrow.
You're home early.
Calvin: Yeah, we finished
the tri-quarterlies today.
The slope gave everybody the day off.
Nice.
It smells really good in here.
It's just a pot roast and some soup.
Hmm.
- You want to go shoot some hoops? Yeah?
- Yeah.
Maybe we'll go play and mommy
will let us know when dinner's ready?
Don't beat me like you did
last time, though, okay?
- Will you take it easy on your old man?
- Hank: I will.
Calvin: I'm pretty sure
I'm going to beat you, though.
Lucas: Where would you start?
Kai: With the foothills. The boedickers.
Lucas: I heard they got burned down.
Kai: Aaron boedicker's still alive.
Hey, boedicker.
Remember me?
Where were you four nights ago?
Fuck you.
I'm not gonna ask you again!
I don't know what the fuck you want,
but I'm not telling you shit.
You took my fucking hand.
Rebecca bowman got killed four days ago.
Fucking bitch had it coming.
Yeah, see, when you say things like that,
that makes me think
you had something to do with it.
Oh, you can torture me all you want,
you fucking sadist,
but I'm only gonna tell you two things.
I didn't kill her,
and I don't give a shit she's dead.
You do know something.
Oh, I know a lot of things.
You know how a guy with no hands
wipes his ass?
I've... I've got a nephew.
Eljay.
Thinks he's some kind of rock star.
He was fucking her for a while.
Where do I find him?
I don't know where he stays,
but he plays nights at this shithole
called snake eyes.
It's off the connector.
I find out you're lying to me,
I come back for the other hand.
You're not welcome around here.
I better get going, then.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Want to bet?
Looks like you're gonna
end up full of holes.
Not before I put one
big fucking hole in you.
- Okay, let's break it up!
- Man: God damn it.
Now.
Most cops know better
than to come into the hills.
Most assholes know better
than to talk back to me.
Something makes me
think if I start looking,
I'm gonna find a lot of
outstanding warrants standing here.
So, you are following me around.
Yeah, I thought that was obvious
by the way I pulled up
right at the Nick of time to save your ass.
What are you doing here, hood?
Just visiting an old friend.
I'm guessing you're working an angle.
That Rebecca was killed
by one of her uncle's enemies.
I'm not working any angles.
You're the sheriff now.
This is your fucking mess.
Yeah, and you're still a person of interest
in this mess.
Does that mean you're gonna follow me
all fucking day?
Yeah, well, believe it or not, hood,
I've got better things to do with my time.
Good.
And you're welcome, by the way!